Guide to the University Archives Web Archive Collection, 2010-ongoing UA.01.15.0014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
University Archives Web Archive collection
2010-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. University Archives
UA.01.15.0014
5427.2 Gigabytes
The University Archives Web Archives Collection was compiled by University Archives staff beginning in 2010. The majority of the collection are Duke University-affiliated sites, either built on domains owned by the University or on external platforms by affiliated offices, departments, or organizations. Website snapshots include those of administrative offices, academic departments, athletic teams, public relations offices, publications, and student organizations. Also included are some websites related to individual faculty, controversies involving Duke community members, and web content related to student activism.
Access to Collection
Some materials in this collection are electronic records that require special equipment. Contact Research Services with questions.
Historical note
The University Archives Web Archives Collection was compiled by University Archives staff beginning in 2010. The collection was built using the Internet Archive's Archive-It service for capturing and preserving web-based digital content.
Organization of the Collection
This collection is organized into series:
1, Administration Series, 2010-ongoing
2, Academics Series, 2010-ongoing
3, Athletics Series, 2010-ongoing
4, Public Relations Series, 2010-ongoing
5, Student Organizations Series, 2010-ongoing
6, Campus Controversies Series, 2010-ongoing
7, Miscellaneous Series, 2014-ongoing
8, Publications Series, 2010-ongoing
9, Student Activism Series, 2015-ongoing
Collection Overview
The University Archives Web Archive Collection consists of approximately website snapshots harvested between 2010 and the present. The majority of the collection are Duke University-affiliated sites, either built on domains owned by the University or on external platforms by affiliated offices, departments, or organizations.
The collection is arranged into eight series: Administration, Academics, Athletics, Public Relations, Student Organizations, Campus Controversies, Miscellaneous, Publications, and Student Activism. The Administration Series includes websites of Duke administrative offices and units. The Academics Series includes websites of academic colleges, departments, and programs, as well as research institutes, interdisciplinary programs, and materials related to faculty. The Athletics Series includes websites of the Duke Athletics program as well as student-run club athletics. The Public Relations Series includes websites related to Duke's communication with employees, the government, students, and the general public. The Student Organizations Series is the largest grouping in the collection, and includes websites of general interest groups, the Greek system, honors societies, selective living groups, arts organizations, political and social cause organizations, religious and cultural organizations, service organizations, and student government. The Campus Controversies Series includes websites collected about controversial events involving Duke and its student body. The Miscellaneous Series consists of several websites that do not fit into the above series.The Publications Series consists of the websites of various publications produced by Duke and Duke-affiliated organizations. The Student Activism series consists of websites, social media content, and individual blog posts and online articles related to various movements on campus led by students.
Due to the size of the collection, the techniques and tools of web harvesting, and the evolving nature of the Internet, some websites have been crawled more comprehensively than others and are represented more faithfully than others.
Provenance
The University Archives Web Archive Collection was compiled by the University Archives from a variety of sources using Archive-It, Twarc, Social Feed Manager, and Twitter Archive Google Sheet (TAGS), 2010-ongoing.
Related Materials
In addition to the View links throughout the collection guide, one may also browse and search URLs harvested with Archive-It for this collection at this URL: https://archive-it.org/collections/1858
Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Buildings; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Athletics; Duke University -- Periodicals; Duke University -- Fraternities and sororities; Duke University -- Student life; Duke University -- Public relations; Duke University -- Students
- Administration Series, 2010-ongoing; 1
  - Academic Council of Duke University, 2010-ongoing
  - Board of Trustees, 2010-ongoing
  - Construction Blog, 2015
  - Drones @ Duke, 2016-ongoing
  - Duke Engage, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke University Web Directory, 2011-ongoing
  - Duke University Website, 2010-ongoing
  - Interdisciplinary Studies, 2010-ongoing
  - Office of Research Support, 2010-ongoing
  - Office of the Provost, 2010-ongoing
  - Office of the University Registrar, 2010-ongoing
  - Policies of Duke University, 2010-ongoing
  - Sustainable Duke, 2010-ongoing
  - West Union Renovation, 2012-ongoing
  - Office of the President Subseries, 2010-ongoing
    - Office of the President, 2010-ongoing
    - Vincent Price: A Greeting to the Duke Community, published in Duke Today, 2016
    - Duke University Names New President, article published in the News & Observer, 2016
    - Is the 'Price' Right? Live interview published in The Chronicle, 2016
  - Student Affairs subseries, 2010-ongoing
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries includes Webpages associated with the Office of Student Affairs. Some areas targeted specifically by the University Archives include the Women's Center and Twitter streams for both the Women's Center and the Center for Sexual and Gender Diversity. Other areas under the aegis of the Office of Student Affairs, including student conduct policies as well as Title IX and sexual misconduct policies, can be found in the webpages captured under the Student Affairs top-level website.
    - Office of Student Affairs, 2010-ongoing
      Parts of the website have been captured since 2010, though the site was not crawled comprehensively until 2013.
    - Office of Student Affairs - Our Cultures Are Not Costumes Tumblr, 2016-ongoing
    - Office of Student Affairs - Women's Center, 2010-ongoing
    - Office of Student Affairs - Duke Women's Center Flickr photostream, 2012-2013
    - Office of Student Affairs - Women's Center Twitter Stream, 2012-ongoing
    - Office of Student Affairs - Center for Sexual and Gender Diversity Twitter Stream, 2013-2015
  - Office of Durham and Community Affairs, 2020-ongoing
  - Office for Institutional Equity, 2020-ongoing
  - Office of the Executive Vice President, 2020-ongoing
  - Return To Duke, 2021-ongoing
  - Duke Performances, 2021-ongoing
  - Duke Learning Innovation, 2021-ongoing
- Academics Series, 2010-ongoing; 2
  - Bass Connections, 2014-ongoing
  - Bass Connections Project Teams, 2017-ongoing
  - Long-Term Soil Ecosystem Studies, 2010-2012
  - Center for Philosphy, Arts, and Literature, 2010-ongiong
  - Divinity School, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Kunshan University Blog, 2013-ongoing
  - Academic Resource Center, 2010-ongoing
  - American Grand Strategy, 2010-ongoing
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 2011-ongoing
  - Department of Computer Science, 2010-ongoing
  - Department of Evolutionary Biology, 2010-ongoing
  - Department of Political Science, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Center for Genomic and Computational Biology, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Center for Health Informatics, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Institute for Brain Sciences, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Robotics, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Service-Learning, 2013-ongoing
  - Duke University Archives, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke University Libraries, 2010-ongoing
  - Global Health Institute, 2010-ongoing
  - Humanities Writ Large, 2011-ongoing
  - Humanities, Arts, Science, and Technology Advanced Collaboratory (HASTAC), 2010-ongoing
  - Kenan Institute for Ethics, 2010-ongoing
  - Naval ROTC, 2010-ongoing
  - Nicholas Institute for Environmental Policy Solutions, 2010-ongoing
  - Nicholas School of the Environment - Southern Center for Sustainable Forests, 2011-2013
  - Pratt School of Engineering - Smart Home Program, 2010-ongoing
  - Sanford School of Public Policy - Undergraduate Major in Public Policy, 2013-ongoing
  - Scholars@Duke, 2014-ongoing
  - Science and Society, 2014-ongoing
  - Social Science Research Institute, 2010-ongoing
  - Trinity College of Arts & Sciences, 2010-ongoing
  - University Scholars Program, 2010-2012
  - Faculty Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 4
    - Faculty Database System, 2010-ongoing
    - Faculty Database System entry for Frank L. Borchardt, 2011
    - Frank L. Borchardt Memorial, 2011
    - Honoring Frank Borchardt, 2010-2011
    - Professor Jedediah Purdy's blog, 2011-2020
  - John Hope Franklin Humanities Institute Subseries, 2013-ongoing; 3
    - John Hope Franklin Humanities Institute, 2010-ongoing
    - John Hope Franklin Humanities Institute Portal homepage, 2013-ongoing
    - Aesthetics of the Anthropocene project site, 2013-ongoing
    - Audiovisualities Lab lab site, 2013-ongoing
    - BorderWork(s) Lab lab site, 2013-ongoing
    - Consortium of Humanities Centers and Institutes, 2015
    - Defining Lines: Cartography in the Age of Empire project site, 2013-ongoing
    - Digital History Working Group project site, 2013-ongoing
    - Ecology of Networks project site, 2013-ongoing
    - Greater than Games lab site, 2013-ongoing
    - Haiti Lab site, 2013-ongoing
    - Humanitarianism in Haiti: Visions and Practice project site, 2013-ongoing
    - PhD Lab in Digital Knowledge lab site, 2013-ongoing
    - SoundBox: Sonic Transfer, Social Amplification project site, 2013-ongoing
    - Unifinished Journey: Writing American History, 2013-2014
    - Voudou Archive project site, 2013
  - School of Law Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 2
    - School of Law, 2010-ongoing
    - Scholarship Repository, 2010-2014
    - The Goodson Blogson: News and Announcements from the J. Michael Goodson Law Library, 2011-ongoing
    - Duke Law Campus Speech Database, 2021-ongoing
    - Wilson Center for Science and Justice, 2021-ongoing
    - Judicature, 2021-ongoing
    - Climate Risk Disclosure Lab, 2021-ongoing
    - Bolch Judicial Institute at Duke Law, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke Center for Firearms Law, 2021-ongoing
    - ODonnell Monitor, 2021-ongoing
    - Ten Years from the Bottom, 2021
    - Too Big To Ignore - How Climate Change Threatens Financial Stability, 2021
    - The FinReg Blog, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke Law Forensics Forum, 2021-ongoing
    - Lawfire Blog, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke Law Center for Science and Justice Blog, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke Law Tech Lab, 2021-ongoing
    - Duke Law Class of 2021 Graduation webpage, 2021-ongoing
  - School of Medicine Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 1
    - Duke Doctor of Physical Therapy program, 2010-ongoing
    - Department of Psychology and Behavioral Sciences, 2011-2013
    - Department of Radiology, 2010-2014
  - Transcultural Islam Research Network, 2017
  - Islamicommentary, 2017
  - Graduate Liberal Studies, 2012-2016, 2020-ongoing
  - Duke Forum for Scholars and Publics, 2020-ongoing
  - Department of Gender, Sexuality & Feminist Studies, 2020-ongoing
  - Duke Talent Identification Program (Duke TIP), 2020-ongoing
  - Duke Graduate School, 2020-ongoing
- Athletics Series, 2010-ongoing; 3
  - Dancing Devils, 2010, 2015-2016
  - Duke Blue Planet, 2011-2018
  - Duke Crew, 2010
  - Duke Hockey, 2010-ongoing
  - GoDuke: The Official Website of Duke Athletics, 2010-ongoing
  - Club Sports Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 5
    - Sports Club Council, 2010
    - Club Badminton, 2010
    - Club Baseball, 2010
    - Club Bass Fishing Team, 2010-2012
    - Club Cycling, 2010-2015
    - Club Equestrian Team, 2010-ongoing
    - Club Field Hockey, 2010-2011
    - Club Golf, 2010-2012
    - Club Martial Arts (BJJ), 2010-2011
    - Club Men's Basketball, 2010-2011
    - Club Men's Lacrosse, 2010-2012
    - Club Men's Soccer, 2010-2011
    - Club Men's Tennis, 2010-2011
    - Club Men's Ultimate Frisbee, 2010
    - Club Men's Volleyball, 2010-2011
    - Club Motorsports, 2012-2015
    - Club Rugby Football, 2010-ongoing
    - Club Running, 2010-ongoing
    - Club Shotokan Karate, 2010-2013
    - Club Skating, 2010
    - Club Ski and Snowboard, 2010-ongoing
    - Club Softball, 2010
    - Club Swimming, 2010
    - Club Table Tennis, 2010-2011
    - Club Triathalon, 2010-ongoing
    - Club Water Polo, 2010
    - Club Women's Basketball, 2010
    - Club Women's Lacrosse, 2010
    - Club Women's Rugby, 2010-2012
    - Club Women's Soccer, 2010-2011
    - Club Women's Tennis, 2010-2011
    - Club Women's Ultimate Frisbee, 2010
    - Club Women's Volleyball, 2010-2011
    - Club Wrestling, 2010-2011
    - Fuqua United - MBA Soccer Club, 2010
- Public Relations Series, 2010-ongoing; 4
  - CDS Porch: News from the Center for Documentary Studies, 2011-ongoing
  - Duke Today, 2011-ongoing
  - Duke Today News, 2010-2013
  - Duke Today RSS feed (superseded), 2010-2011
  - Events@Duke, 2011-ongoing
  - Jane Goodall Archive Showcase, 2011-2013
  - Office of Federal Relations, 2010-ongoing
  - Working@Duke, 2011-ongoing
  - Office of News & Communications, 2013-ongoing
- Student Organizations Series, 2010-ongoing; 6
  - American Assembly for Men in Nursing, 2010
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 2010-2013
  - American Society of Civil Engineers - Duke University Student Chapter, 2010
  - Animal Law Society, 2010-2012
  - Asian Business Club, 2010-ongoing
  - Association for India's Development, 2010-2013
  - Bench and Bar Prelaw Society, 2010-2012
  - Biology Majors Union, 2010-2014
  - Biomedical Engineering Society, 2010-2013
  - Blackjack Team, 2010
  - Black Graduate & Professional Student Association, 2010-2012
  - Blue Devil's District, 2011-2013
  - Black Student Alliance, 2010-ongoing
  - Chemistry Majors Union, 2010-2011
  - Consulting Club, 2010-ongoing
  - Culinary Society, 2010
  - Discover Worlds, 2010
  - Duke Air Force ROTC, 2012-ongoing
  - Duke American Medical Association, 2013
  - Duke Anime Club, 2010-2012
  - Duke Apiary Club, 2010
  - Duke Arts & Crafts Club, 2011
  - Duke Association for Business-Oriented Women (BOW), 2010-2016
  - Duke-BOW website, 2017-2020
  - Duke Association for Greater Gaming Education and Recreation, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Blue Rose Society, 2014
  - Duke Chapter of the Association for Computing Machinery, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Coffeehouse, 2010-2011
  - Duke Engineers for International Development, 2012
  - Duke German Club, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Groups Directory, 2012-ongoing
  - Duke Honor Council, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Innovative Design Agency (DiDA), 2010-2012; 2016
  - Duke Marketing Club, 2010
  - Duke Math Union, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke MBA Entrepreneurship and Venture Capital Club, 2010
  - Duke Microfinance Leadership Initiative, 2011-2012
  - Duke Mock Trial, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Moot Court, 2014-ongoing
  - Duke Outing Club, 2010-2012
  - Duke Philosophical Society, 2010
  - Duke Physics Graduate Student Organization, 2010-2013
  - Duke Private Equity Club, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Real Estate Cooperative, 2010-2011
  - Duke Start-Up Challenge, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke Undergraduate Bioethics Society, 2010-2012
  - Duke University Emergency Medical Services, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke University Model United Nations Conference, 2010-ongoing
  - Duke University National Society of Black Engineers, 2010
  - Duke University Union Major Attractions Committee, 2010-2012
  - Duke Venture Forward, 2012-2013
  - Duke-Durham Chess Club, 2010
  - English Majors' Union, 2010-ongoing
  - Eugene A. Stead Society, 2010-ongoing
  - FEMMES: Females Excelling More in Math, Engineering, and Science, 2010-ongoing
  - Genome Research& Education Society, 2011-2012
  - Hack Duke, 2014-ongoing
  - Indus - South Asian Business Club, 2010
  - International Business Club, 2010-2011
  - K-Ville at Duke University, 2010-ongoing
  - LifeDesign, 2010-2012
  - Mercado Global Duke Chapter, 2010
  - Minority Association of Premedical Students (MAPS), 2010-2012
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Duke Chapter, 2010-2012
  - Net Impact Club, 2010-2019
  - Office of Student Affairs - Student Organization Directory, 2011-2013
  - Plan V - Duke's Vegetarian Club, 2010
  - Project WILD, 2010-2015
  - Prospective Health Care Club, 2010-2011
  - Social Entrepreneur and Enterprise Development for Students (SEEDS), 2010
  - Society of American Foresters - Duke Student Chapter, 2010-ongoing
  - Society of Women Engineers - Duke Section, 2012-ongoing
  - Student Affairs Graduate & Professional Women's Network, 2010-2012
  - Student Affairs Office of Student Activities & Facilities Duke Conversations, 2010-2011
  - Student Affairs Office of Student Activities & Facilities Leadership Roundtable, 2010-2013
  - Student Affairs Step Up: Leadership Development, 2010
  - Student Interest Group in Neurology and Neurosurgery, 2010-ongoing
  - Student National Medical Association, 2011-2013
  - Student organizations associated with the HHMI, 2010
  - Student Registered Nurse Anesthetist Association, 2010-2015
  - Students of the World, 2010
  - Students of the World Facebook page, 2015-ongoing
  - The Navigators, 2010-2012
  - Women's Mentoring Network, 2010-2012
  - Akin, 2019
  - Greek Life Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 8
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life portal, 2015-ongoing
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life - Interfraternity Council, 2010-2012
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life - Inter-Greek Council, 2010-2012
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life - National Pan-Hellenic Council, 2010-2013
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life - Order of Omega, 2010-2013
    - Student Affairs Fraternity & Sorority Life - Panhellenic Association, 2010-2012
    - Alpha Delta Pi Sorority - Omicron Chapter, 2010-2011
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity - Delta Kappa Chapter, 2010-2011
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority - Iota Mu Chapter, 2010
    - Alpha Kappa Delta Phi Sorority - Alpha Beta Chapter, 2012-ongoing
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity - Kappa Omicron Chapter, 2010-2013
    - Alpha Phi Sorority - Beta Nu Chapter, 2010-2016
    - Alpha Tau Omega Fraternity - Xi Chapter, 2010-2013
    - Chi Omega Sorority - Mu Kappa Chapter, 2014-ongoing
    - Chi Psi Fraternity - Alpha Sigma Delta Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Delta Delta Delta - Alpha Omicron Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Delta Gamma Sorority - Beta Theta Chapter, 2010-2012
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity - Epsilon Rho Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Delta Sigma Phi Fraternity - Alpha Epsilon Chapter, 2012-ongoing
    - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority - Lambda Omega Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Delta Tau Delta Fraternity - Delta Kappa Chapter, 2010
    - Kappa Alpha Order - Alpha Phi Chapter, 2010
    - Kappa Alpha Psi - Iota Xi Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Kappa Alpha Theta Sorority - Duke Chapter, 2010
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Sorority - National and Duke chapters, 2010-ongoing
    - Lambda Upsilon Lambda Fraternity - Rho Chapter, 2010
    - Phi Beta Sigma - Alpha Alpha Chi Chapter, 2010-2015
    - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity - NC Alpha Chapter, 2010-2011
    - Pi Beta Phi - North Carolina Beta Chapter, 2010
    - Pi Kappa Alpha Fraternity - Alpha Alpha Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Pi Kappa Phi Fraternity - Mu Chapter, 2010-2015
    - Psi Upsilon Fraternity - Chi Delta Chapter, 2010; 2015-ongoing
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity - North Carolina Nu Colony, 2010-2018
    - Sigma Chi Fraternity - Beta Lambda Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Sigma Nu - Gamma Chapter, 2010-2014
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon Fraternity - North Carolina Gamma Chapter, 2010-2014
    - Theta Nu Xi Multicultural Sorority - Delta Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Zeta Phi Beta Sorority - Nu Omicron Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Zeta Tau Alpha Sorority - Phi Chapter, 2010-ongoing
  - Honors Societies Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 7
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Professional Business Fraternity - Beta Eta Chapter, 2010
    - Alpha Phi Omega Service Fraternity - Lambda Nu Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Delta Sigma Pi, 2016-2018
    - Phi Sigma Pi - Delta Epsilon Chapter, 2010-ongoing
    - Sigma Xi - Duke Chapter, 2010-2013
    - Tau Beta Pi Engineering Honor Society, 2010-2015
  - Selective Living Groups Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 9
    - Arts Theme House, 2011-ongoing
    - Brownstone, 2010-ongoing
    - Maxwell House, 2010-ongoing
    - Mirecourt House, 2010-ongoing
    - Prism Multicultural Selective Living Group, 2011-ongoing
    - Round Table Selective Living Group, 2011-ongoing
    - SHARE, 2010-ongoing
    - The Language House (Langdorm), 2010-ongoing
    - Ubuntu Selective Living Group, 2010-ongoing
    - Wayne Manor, 2010-2016
  - Performing, Visual, and Literary Arts Organizations Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 11
    - Campus Concert Series, 2010-2011
    - Chamber Players, 2010-2015
    - Defining Movement Dance Troupe, 2010-ongoing
    - Deja Blue, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Chinese Dance Troupe, 2010-2014
    - Duke Chinese Dance, 2019-ongoing
    - Duke Chorale, 2010, 2016-ongoing
    - Duke Circus, 2010-2012
    - Duke Players, 2010-2014
    - Duke Student Broadcasting, 2012-ongoing
    - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Improv (DUI), 2010-2018
    - Duke University Marching & Pep Band, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke University Chorale and Chapel Choir, 2013-ongoing
    - Duke University Wind Symphony, 2013-ongoing
    - Freewater Productions, 2012-ongoing
    - Healing Expressions, 2010
    - Hoof 'n Horn, 2010-ongoing
    - Inside Joke, 2010, 2014; 2014
    - Lady Blue, 2010-ongoing
    - Nasher Museum of Art, 2010-ongoing
    - Nasher Museum of Art student opportunities, 2010-ongoing
    - On Tap, 2010, 2015
    - Out of the Blue, 2010-2013
    - Rhythm & Blue, 2010-ongoing
    - Sabrosura Latin Dance Troupe, 2012-ongoing
    - Sapphire, 2010-ongoing
    - Something Borrowed, Something Blue, 2010-2012; 2015-ongoing
    - Speak of the Devil, 2013-ongoing
    - The Pitchforks, 2012-2014
    - Visual Arts Committee, 2010-2011
    - Wendell Theater Group, 2010
    - WXDU - Duke University Radio, 2010-ongoing
  - Political and Social Cause Organizations Subseries, 2010-ongoing; 13
    - ACLU at Duke University, 2013
    - Active Minds at Duke, 2010
    - Amnesty International at Duke, 2010-2012
    - Blue Devils United, 2011-2014
    - Campus BluePrint: Joint Publication of Duke Democrats and UNC Young Democrats, 2010
    - Center for Race Relations, 2010-ongoing
    - Develle Dish, 2011-ongoing
    - Duke Against War, 2010
    - Duke College Republicans, 2010-2011
    - Duke Human Rights Coalition, 2010-2012
    - Duke Libertarian Club, 2010-2015
    - Duke Refugee Aid, 2010-2012
    - Duke Students for Gender Neutrality, 2010-ongoing
    - Duke Students for Life, 2010
    - Duke Students for the Protection of Animals, 2010
    - DukeOUT, 2010-ongoing
    - Environmental Alliance, 2011-ongoing
    - I Need Feminism Twitter Feed, 2012-ongoing
    - International Criminal Court Student Network, 2010-ongoing
    - International Justice Mission Duke Chapter, 2010
    - Purple, 2010
    - Refugee Asylum Support Project, 2012-2013
    - Students Against Sweatshops, 2010
    - Students for Choice, 2010
    - Students to Unite Duke, 2012-ongoing
    - Universities Allied for Essential Medicine, 2010
    - Who Needs Feminism Facebook page, 2012-ongoing
    - Who Needs Feminism? Tumblr, 2012-ongoing
    - Who Needs Feminism? Tumblr RSS feed, 2012-ongoing
    - Duke Disability Alliance, 2018-2020
    - Duke Disability Alliance NeuroDIVERSITY & Inclusion Exhibit, 2017